The Last Godfather is a comedy, crime, romance film directed by Shim Hyung-rae.
Young-goo the son of mafia boss Don Carini, is too
foolish to be part of the mafia elite.
One day, Young-goo comes to his father and is trained
by Tony V to be his father's successor.
A few days later, Young-goo accidentally rescues Nancy, the only
daughter of Don Bonfante, the boss of a rival mafia family.
But Vinnie, an under-boss of the Bonfante family kidnapped her
and fabricates that Young-goo has taken her.
Vinnie's behavior provokes an armed conflict between the two families.
Young-gu, played by Shim Hyung-rae.
Don Carini, played by Harvey Keitel.
Tony V, played by Michael Rispoli.
Vinnie, played by Jason Mewes.
Nancy Bonfante, played by Jocelin Donahue.
Captain O'Brian, played by Blake Clark.
The Last Godfather (Korean: 라스트 갓파더) is a 2010 mafia
comedy film directed by Shim Hyung-rae.
The film explores themes of new york city, mafia, godfather.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.